For four nights straight, the president has been trying to provoke violence here, right here, in the black communities and in the brown communities, having ICE kidnap our neighbors, having the black community be harassed and profiled.
We say, hell no, we won't go.
Black Washingtonians have long recognized that community violence cannot be solved through state violence and have asked for meaningful investments and solutions that are proven to work.
I stand in front of you today with a signal to the residents of D.C. and the country that we will not be idle as oppressive structures try to harm our communities and take power.
The fight for black liberation and the liberation of all people will not stop no matter our oppression, intimidation, manipulation tactics.
We have the right to demand respect, to protect ourselves, and protect each other.
We're fighting against mass incarceration, policing, ICE, violence towards immigrants and Muslims, violence in Palestine, worker exploitation, and more.
We're fighting for freedom and safety for all people, including black, brown, people who are women, feminine, queer, trans, gender non-conforming, immigrants, disability, power, and more.
We're not free until all of us are free.
We will not stand here and allow authoritarianism in Washington, D.C.